{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "4314b865-e08d-4ffb-837a-5021c18c8004",
      "question": "What is pair programming ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "Fri Feb 13 2025 00:22:36 GMT+0100 (heure normale d’Europe centrale)",
      "answeredCorrectly": null
    },
    {
      "id": "a208718a-9f5d-4c28-afc0-7d0d47c9e1c7",
      "question": "What is pair programming test ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer. test ",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "Fri Feb 11 2025 00:23:45 GMT+0100 (heure normale d’Europe centrale)",
      "answeredCorrectly": null
    },
    {
      "id": "3e4f4368-ba3a-48f3-90b3-bc6375665cb2",
      "question": " test test ",
      "answer": " test ",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "Fri Feb 10 2025 00:24:37 GMT+0100 (heure normale d’Europe centrale)",
      "answeredCorrectly": null
    },
    {
      "id": "d167230c-5401-4544-8aed-4ac9d2c1484e",
      "question": " test test 2 ",
      "answer": " test 2 ",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "Fri Feb 14 2025 00:24:51 GMT+0100 (heure normale d’Europe centrale)",
      "answeredCorrectly": null
    },
    {
      "id": "e52fdd18-78ca-40e4-9010-8d8fa965f04e",
      "question": "What is pair pzdqszdqsograeeeeemming ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work inzdqsdzqsdqsdqqsdz pair on same computer.",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "2025-02-14T10:25:09.586Z",
      "answeredCorrectly": false
    },
    {
      "id": "b2a0ea97-f830-4d5c-9926-02be6a3b57b0",
      "question": "test ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "2025-02-14T10:46:51.615Z",
      "answeredCorrectly": false
    },
    {
      "id": "526c55ec-4915-4516-b4fb-45037438cee2",
      "question": "test ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "Fri Feb 12 2025 11:32:38 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)",
      "answeredCorrectly": null
    },
    {
      "id": "ec800eb2-eacc-4ffc-9c6a-747b4073c64b",
      "question": "test ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "DONE",
      "date": "2025-02-15T18:45:20.130Z",
      "answeredCorrectly": true
    },
    {
      "id": "6a83e6da-5263-4d1f-8cfa-6c6507fe86e9",
      "question": "test ?",
      "answer": "Azdsqzdqspractice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "DONE",
      "date": "2025-02-15T18:33:07.991Z",
      "answeredCorrectly": true
    },
    {
      "id": "05a084e2-63ac-4d5a-ad5b-b67e4de65197",
      "question": "What is pair programming ?",
      "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
      "category": "FIRST",
      "date": "2025-02-16T12:12:37.631Z",
      "answeredCorrectly": false
    }
  ]
}